Hey everybody, we are joined by Packers
general manager Brian Gutekunst. And
Goody, it seems like you've had a busy
day. Let's see, you signed Jayden Reed
to a contract extension, you made a
trade, and you drafted two players. Have
you been rather busy? It's been a It's
been a good day for the Packers, and um
you know, yeah, our staff's been busy.
Um but um
you know, I think certainly signing
signing Jayden, and he's a winner. He's
been a great player for us.
Um that was really exciting to start the
day off, and then the beginning of the
draft finally get a pick, you know,
after missing yesterday, and getting two
players that you know, I really really
like, our staff really likes, our
coaching staff likes, and uh and and we
think they'll be really good Packers.
Talking about those two players, Brandon
SeeSauce.
Corner out of South Carolina. What
really attracted you to him? Yeah, he's
got you know, he's almost 6 ft. He's got
good length, really good feet, excellent
transition quickness.
Uh he can run. Uh he's very aggressive
and competitive, and I think that's uh
that's what drew us to him. He started
at NC State, was really good player
there, transferred to South Carolina in
the SEC, and had a really good year this
year.
Um we just think that um again, he's
very young, um but we think he's a
really good player now with a with a ton
of upside. Yeah, just 20 years old.
That's almost unheard of, isn't it?
Yeah, Kenny Clark-like, you know what I
mean? So hopefully he could turn out
that good. But yeah, he's one of the
younger players in the draft, and um
again, but very mature young man, and uh
very very intense and and and football
is very important to him. Him being a
great player is very important to him.
So we think he's going to fit here very
well with our with our team and then our
culture here. You know, seeing the video
I've seen on him, he's not bashful
whatsoever about the rough stuff. He'll
stick his nose in there. Absolutely.
He's uh again, he can play off, he can
play press, he'll tackle, you know, so
again, you know, all these guys are
going to have to learn the the NFL game
and what this is all about cuz it is
different than what they've experienced.
But we think that his skill set really
does lend itself to be a pretty good
player in this league. In the third
round, you make a trade, move up to
select Chris McLellan out of Missouri,
defensive tackle. What attracted you to
him? Yeah, first of all, you know, he's
6'4, he's 315 lb. He can stop the run,
he holds the point very very well. He's
a very He also is a very good pass
rusher. He can play up and down the
line, so he's very versatile, which
obviously, as you know, we like very
much. And again, played in the SEC,
played in the league where that matters.
And um so again, he's a young player,
proven already uh at a very high level
in college, and we think he's going to
be a really good fit here. Looks like,
and this is always sometimes, I think,
or maybe it used to be, a concern with
the big guys, he's got a good motor. He
does.
>> he he brings it.
>> Yeah, he plays hard, played a lot of
snaps there. I think he was at probably
60-some percent, and did everything. He
was not one of those guys that came off
the field a lot on third down. He played
a lot, and like you said, he can rush
the passer. So you know, a tremendous
upside, and I think he'll be a good fit
for our team. Have you ever drafted a
guy before with 11-in
hands? Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> I I I pay money just to look at his
hands.
>> Yeah, interestingly enough, we had Sean
Ryan, right? Sean Ryan, 11-in hands,
yeah. Uh we've had a few guys here and
there that that have gotten to that that
level. But yeah, he's like I said, he's
a big man now, and um he's going to add
some size in there, and uh certainly
that was something that was was
important to us. Has the draft in
general been falling the right way as
far as you're concerned? Yeah, I think
it did for us today. You know, I think
uh the board held up very well. We had a
number of choices at 52, and then a
number of choices [music] in the third
round. I think uh certainly with
Christopher, we felt that he was one of
those players that we we felt we needed
to go get. Uh not necessarily cuz we
were for we're for sure that he was
going to get taken. Uh we shouldn't We
didn't know that, but we thought um his
value was was right to do that. I don't
know how much you can say, but can you
offer some sort of scouting report for
how you're approaching tomorrow?
Yeah, I think we're just we're always
going to let the board talk to us a
little bit, and try to get into the
areas where we think it's strong.
Uh there's a lot of good players left up
there that we really think could help
us, and so we'll we'll kind of um you
know, just monitor as it goes, but um we
won't be afraid to be aggressive if the
right guy is there.
Um and we won't be afraid to to move
down and add picks as well. But um you
know, again, I think I like I like our
football team right now. I like our
roster. So um you know, we're going to
try to add some quality players
tomorrow. We're excited about it. Bottom
line, Goody, did you get better tonight?
Did you feel that? Yeah, I think again,
starting with Jayden, you know, and and
doing that extension with him. I mean,
that was really important for us. We got
we got a lot of work to do with you
know, some extensions as we go
um you know, over the next few months
that that'll be important for us, and
that was a good start. And um and
certainly the draft finally, you know,
watching 51 guys come off the board
before you get the pick is not something
I you know, like to do, but um ended up
getting a
player like Brandon and Christopher, I
think that was really important for us.
When you go into a draft with Micah
Parsons as your first-round draft
choice, do you kind of feel like you're
playing with the house's money? A little
bit there? Yeah, a little bit. You know,
that's uh
I told him today that you know, when
when it was our pick at 20, what was
supposed to be our pick at 20, we had
his card up. He was ready to go. But uh
um yeah, certainly looking back on that,
no regrets there. Certainly we uh we
that's one of those things that uh
certainly how he played last year, we're
pretty excited about him coming back.
Goody, good luck tomorrow. Thanks for
the time.